Carlos Martínez

Buenos Aires, Argentina · <u>linkedin.com/in/carlosmartoz</u> · +54 6835 8377 · carlosmrtzo@gmail.com

Front-End Developer with 3 years of experience specializing in creating and designing user interfaces for the web using technologies such as React.js, Next.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS. I also have experience using Figma for interface design. I am always eager to learn new technologies, have strong communication skills, and excel both in team settings and working independently.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Tecnosoftware

Buenos Aires, Argentina

January 2024 - Present

Front-End Developer

- I handle a custom Front-End framework for ATMs using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and JSON.
- I am responsible for multiple unit tests to validate the previous development work I perform.
- I develop interfaces tailored to the needs of each project within the company's internal framework.
- I perform analysis and monitoring of potential bugs and new software developments through logs.

Wiper Agency

Buenos Aires, Argentina

September 2023 – October 2024

Front-End Developer

- I was in charge of the entire front-end of the project within the team.
- I implemented AI-powered chats in several projects on the front-end side.
- I integrated all the endpoints provided by the back-end team with the front-end.
- I translated designs created in Figma into code using React.js and Next.js with high fidelity.

Grupo MContigo

Salamanca, España

Front-End Developer

April 2022 – June 2023

- I created documentation for new team members.
- I developed websites, components, and widgets using React.js and Next.js.
- I conceptualized designs using Figma and translated them into code with high fidelity.

EDUCATION

RAFAEL BELLOSO CHACÍN UNIVERSITY

Maracaibo, Venezuela

November 2019

Honors: Degree in Computer Engineering and Diploma in

Webmaster

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Computer Engineering

• Native in Spanish. English B1.